http://www.barcodeproducts.co.nz/about-us/privacy-policy

TestimonialsLoginCart Newsletter03 341 1345CallEmailSearchMenuProductsBarcode ScannersBarcode Label PrintersPOS Systems & HardwareLabel StickersAndroid Mobile Barcode ScannerAccessoriesServicesFree Barcode GeneratorSolutionsInventory & Stock TrackingAsset Tracking SolutionsInventory Software for XeroLabels, Label Stickers, Metal LabelsWarehouse Management SolutionsItem Rental Management SolutionAbout UsWho/What/HowShippingReturns PolicyPrivacy PolicyTerms of TradePayment optionsFAQBarcodes infoAbout BarcodesBenefits of Using BarcodesContactPrivacy Policy
Privacy Principles
We value the trust you extend to us when you register your details with us.  Our aim is to keep you briefed about the technology we supply.  Any information we gather at this web site is strictly for our use and is not shared with any other entity, public or private, for any reason.  We will not sell, rent or give away any lists or other data that we keep and we do not buy such information from other sources.
Statistical Data
Like most servers, we track IP addresses and referring pages to help with site maintenance and improvements. This data is viewed only as anonymous statistics to show the busiest times of the day or week, pages with errors and how effective our advertising has been. This information is not used for any other purpose.
Personal Information Collected - Order Forms
With the exception of credit card info (which is not stored but retained by our banking partners), we store the information from your order form to allow us to provide technical support or customer service.  You may elect to have your information completely removed from this system by e-mailing us at info@barcodeproducts.co.nz with your request.
Personal Information Collected - Newsletter Subscriptions
When you subscribe to our newsletter, you will receive a weekly special offer and monthly barcode-related newsletter.  All newsletters carry the ability to unsubscribe.  You can contact us to remove you by e-mailing us at info@barcodeproducts.co.nz with your request.
Correction or Removal of your Information
If you wish to correct, update or remove any information about you that may be in our records, please send us an e-mail at info@barcodeproducts.co.nz with the details of your request. If you wish to contact us further, please find complete contact information on our contact page.
What happens if we decide to change this Privacy Policy?
If we change any part of our Privacy Policy we will post these changes on this page so that you are always aware of how we are treating your personal information.
Storage of personal information
As required by the Privacy Act 1993, Barcode Products Limited follows strict procedures when storing and using the information you have provided.  All information is stored on password protected computers with firewall protection.Barcode ScannersBarcode Label PrintersLabel StickersAndroid Mobile Barcode ScannerFacebookTwitterLinkedInYouTubeUnit B, 13 Parkhouse RoadWigram Christchurch 8042 New ZealandMapEmail03 341 13450800 862 272© Copyright 2020 Barcode Products Ltd. Built by Tech Agency Limited Christchurch. Powered by Airsquare.Added to cartContinue shoppingView cart & checkout
